<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><modules><module><id><![CDATA[2937]]></id><name><![CDATA[storemanagerforprestashop]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Store Manager for PrestaShop]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Administrative tools]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[30-DAY FREE TRIAL!&nbsp;&nbsp;The back office solution you need to run your PrestaShop online store efficiently ! Store Manager for PrestaShop&nbsp;will save you over 2 hours a day by automating daily]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/administration-tools-prestashop-modules/2937-store-manager-for-prestashop.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2937.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[30-DAY FREE TRIAL!&nbsp;&nbsp;The back office solution you need to run your PrestaShop online store efficiently ! Store Manager for PrestaShop&nbsp;will save you over 2 hours a day by automating daily tasks&nbsp;and making it simple to update your shop. &nbsp; Store Manager for PrestaShop is a desktop application, designed to speed up and automate the management of PrestaShop based stores. Not only does it take care of the mass operations with products, categories, orders and customers extending the functionality of the store web back-end, but also lines up with an intuitive interface and advanced addons for easy store management. Save your time, money, and resources by allowing Store Manager for PrestaShop do all the job for you. Store Manager for PrestaShop will make your store stand out from the crowd! &nbsp; *** WINNER OF THE PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE *** &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save your time, money, and resources by allowing Store Manager for PrestaShop do all the job for you. Store Manager for PrestaShop will make your store stand out from the crowd! &nbsp; Spend an Hour, Save a Day! Store Manager for PrestaShop was designed to work for you and not at the expense of your business. It is your personal assistant that does all the routine tasks, saving you tons of time for greater deeds. For that matter, it provides with ready-made export/import features, report tools, advanced addons, etc. No need to spend a day getting deep into how your store works, spend an hour understanding how Store Manager does the job for you. &nbsp; Take Your Online Business to the Bank Buy one Store Manager instead of multiple modules. Use one Store Manager license to manage your multiple stores. Store Manager doesn&rsquo;t require any special skills, so you don&rsquo;t have to pay someone to keep your store database organized. You can implement all the necessary updates yourself with Store Manager for PrestaShop and get on to important tasks. &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[]]></version><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[http://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/689783-pprod/store-manager-for-prestashop.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/689783-pbig/store-manager-for-prestashop.jpg]]></big></cover></module></modules>